KEVIN BURGESS

8 Anniston Way, Greenville SC,29617 · 302-559-9409 kfburge@g.clemson.edu · https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevin-burgess-462454173 https://kfburge.github.io/KevinBurgess/generic.html (kfburge.github.io)

Highly motivated Clemson University graduate studying Japanese and international business. Looking for opportunities to apply myself to international relations in business and operations where I can utilize my professional experience and knowledge to contribute to international business and marketing.

EXPERIENCE

AUGUST 2022- CURRENT

SALES & TECHNICAL SPECIALIST, VERIZON CORPORATE LOCATION GREER, SC

Duties included communicating with both consumer and business accounts on telecommunications services and products. This position requires strong communication skills to understand client's needs and help provide tailored solutions to their business and personal lives. Lead the store in sale volume and exceeded internal metric requirements.

JUNE 2021 – AUGUST 2021

MARKETING RESEARCHER, GOWITHGUIDES

An internship with Travelience, a Japanese tour company that sells tours internationally. I worked as a market researcher to learn about the tour market of each location by researching popular destinations as well as prices, target consumers, and tourist feedback to create a tour that would sell well. A few of the locations I completed include Rome, Kyoto, Tokyo, and Paris.

JUNE 2019 - MARCH 2020

FRONT DESK AGENT, HILTON EMBASSY SUITES DOWNTOWN GREENVILLE

Embassy Suites Downtown Greenville front desk operations including assisting guest with their itinerary plans, local attractions, and restaurants. Utilized my knowledge of the downtown area to act as concierge for dinner reservations, travel accommodations, etc. Anticipating guest needs, punctually addressing concerns, managing guest temperament, and formulating solutions.

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2018 - MAY 2022

JAPANESE LANGUAGE & INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS, CLEMSON UNIVERSITY

3.54 GPA Senior, Japanese Professional Society, Dean's List 2018-2022

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2018

ASSOCIATE IN ARTS, GREENVILLE TECHNICAL COLLEGE

3.49 GPA, Honors Program Graduate, Dean's List 2016-2018 2017 South Regional Honors Conference Presenter and Speaker on Japanese Isolationism

SKILLS

- Experience in consumer and B2B sales
- Excellent Communicator
- Intermediate Writing & Verbal Skills in Japanese
- Experience with HTML
- Proficient with Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Adobe Photoshop, OnQ, Popular social media platforms